Silent night
Starry night
夜寂静
夜繁星
All is calm
万物静
All is bright
万物明
'Round the forest, parents and young
森林环绕  不分老少
Gentle creatures everyone
皆是温和的生灵
Home in burrows deep
安家洞穴深处
Home in their burrows deep
安家在洞穴深处
Silent night
夜寂静
Starry night
夜繁星
Snowfall makes the meadows white
落雪把草地刷白
Huddle close to keep family warm
相互依偎留住温情
Tomorrow's dawn will bring Christmas morn
黎明将迎来圣诞清晨
Now the day is done
昨日已经离开
Now that the day is done
平安夜已离开
Silent night
夜寂静
Starry night
夜繁星
Leaves are still and the moon's in sight
叶落定月光尽收眼底
Dreams are born as their eyes fall closed
双眼闭上进入梦乡
Tomorrow's gift is that nobody knows
明日惊喜谁能想象
Sleep in beautiful peace
睡得甜美安详
Oh-whoa
Oh-whoa-oh-oh
Sleep in beautiful peace
睡得甜美安详
翻译
轮回
润色
包子  傻猫
校对
森林金雨  傻猫
背景图绘制
月魇
时间轴
BronyDee
制作
习成 PBU 工作组
感谢观看